### MITCHELL DROHAN

ABOUT ME

SKILLS

I am a full-stack web developer who enjoys learning new tech and applying it to modern, ground-breaking applications. I have experience with web design, code refactoring, peer code reviews and web server configuration. I hope to find a job where I can express my creativity while working with a team to make contributions to the web community.

Vue: [95%]
CSS/HTML5: 85%
Ruby on Rails: 75%
NodeJS: 60%
Scrum/Agile Developement: 76%
Git: (90%)

WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Fluid Media - Full Stack Developer

2017 - present

Created complex web apps using ES6 and HTML5.

Wrote javascript web components using Vue.js and learned to manage application state using VueX.

Created and maintained code for server side technologies such as MySQL, Ruby on Rails and Node.js.

Refactored code for maintainability and worked to ensure the code base adheared to SOLID principles.

Mastered version control using Git.

Learned to deploy web apps using AWS and Capistrano.

## Mohawk College - Quality Assurance Developer

2016 - 2017

- Developed front-end features in AngularJS.

  Worked as a member of an agile team of developers to create the Immunization Connect Ontario Website.
- 3 Created Protractor/Selenium end-to-end test scripts.

  4 Setup and maintained a continuous integration server for running test scripts using Docker and Jenkins.
- 5 Reported bugs and created JIRA tasks.

#### **Guelph Hydro - Engineering Technologist**

2012 - 2015

- Automated the energy distribution design process using AutoCAD 3D and LISP.
- 2 Updated the Guelph Hydro website.
- Programmed relays at distribution high voltage transformer substations for distribution network protection.

#### **EDUCATION**

## Bachelor's of Technology in Software Engineering

McMaster University

Class of 2017

- Software Design
  Project Management
- 3 Software Architecture
- 4 Computer Security

# Advanced Diploma in Electrical Engineering Technology

Georgian College

Class of 2011

- 1 C++ Programming
- 2 Mathematics for Technology
- 3 Python Application Development